(Sheldon:)I'm unhappy.
(Leonard:)This is delicious.
(Leonard:)Where'd you learn
to make chili?
(Priya:)When I was at
university in England,
(Priya:)my flatmate was
from Texas.
(Leonard:)I hope she wasn't anything
like my flatmate from Texas.
(Priya:)Sheldon is a bit
quirky, isn't he?
(Howard:)Oh, please.
That crazy bastard's looking
(Howard:)at quirky
in the rearview mirror.
(Leonard:)Did you know that,
per our roommate agreement,
(Leonard:)I have to wash my feet
before I get in the shower?
(Leonard:)And not in the sink.
(Leonard:)We each have special buckets.
(Howard:)Raj, did you ever
tell your sister
(Howard:)about the time Sheldon
got punched by Bill Gates?
- Oh, God, you're kidding.
- Nope.
(Raj:)Gates gave a speech
at the university.
(Raj:)Sheldon went up to him
afterwards and said,
"Maybe if you weren't
so distracted
(Raj:)by sick children in Africa,
(Raj:)you could have put a little more
thought into Windows Vista."
(all laughing)
(Leonard:)Bam. Right in the nose.
(Leonard:)Made me proud to own a PC.
(Raj:)I'd like to propose a toast
(Raj:)to a rare and wonderful
Sheldon-free evening.